<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Representational Fluency | Xinyue Jiao</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tag/representational-fluency/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/tag/representational-fluency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Representational Fluency</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu_7613a4a452ac7087.png</url>
      <title>Representational Fluency</title>
      <link>https://example.com/tag/representational-fluency/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AR to Enhance Students’ Representational Fluency</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/ar-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/ar-math/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Jul. 2018 - Mar. 2019 (Principal Investigator: Dr. Xiao Hu)
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
 --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🌟 Project Overview&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This joint research project, conducted in collaboration with Columbia University, Beijing Normal University, and East China Normal University, investigates how augmented reality (AR) can enhance students’ representational fluency and self-efficacy in understanding linear functions. The project focuses on designing and evaluating AR applications to support mathematical concept formation and problem-solving skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🛠️ Key Responsibilities
•	Developed 5 AR apps with varied design features to promote students’ understanding of linear functions.
•	Conducted Design-Based Research (DBR) to iteratively refine the apps and assess their impact on student learning.
•	Collected and analyzed data, including:
•	Quantitative Analysis: Conducted ANOVA to examine differences in learning outcomes.
•	Qualitative Analysis: Coded interviews and reflective journals to uncover patterns in students’ experiences.
•	Co-authored papers to disseminate findings and insights from the study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💡 Research Impact&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project demonstrates how leveraging AR can foster representational fluency and build students’ confidence in mathematical problem-solving. By combining innovative technology with evidence-based research, it contributes to the development of cutting-edge educational tools and pedagogical strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
