<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Xinyue Jiao</title>
    <link>https://example.com/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu_7613a4a452ac7087.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Inquiry in AR Learning Environments</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/collaboration-in-arle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/collaboration-in-arle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Jul. 2017 - Jun. 2021 (Principal Investigator: Dr. Xiao Hu)
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

 --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Focusing on the effects of integrating collaborative scripts into AR inquiry activities. Using learning analytics methods, such as cluster analysis, Lag Sequential Analysis, etc., to analyze students&amp;rsquo; collaborative inquiry performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🌟 Project Overview&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project investigates the influence of collaborative scripts and group interaction patterns on middle school students’ collaborative inquiry outcomes in AR learning environments. It aims to understand how structured collaboration impacts knowledge acquisition and group dynamics in immersive educational settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🔍 Research Objectives
1.	Examine the effect of collaborative scripts on group interaction and inquiry outcomes.
2.	Analyze group interaction patterns to identify collaborative behaviors that foster learning.
3.	Develop strategies for enhancing collaboration in AR-based learning activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🛠️ Methodology
•	Data Collection: Pre-tests, group worksheets, post-tests, delayed post-tests, and video recordings of group activities.
•	Data Analysis: ANCOVA, t-tests for outcomes, and lag sequential analysis for interaction behavior patterns.
•	Assessment: Evaluated collaborative inquiry performance across five dimensions (knowledge understanding, role division, interaction participation, coordination supervision, and cooperation atmosphere).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Augmented Reality Learning Environment</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/intelligent-arle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/intelligent-arle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Aug. 2020 - Present (Principal Investigator: Dr. Xiao Hu)
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
 --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🌟 Project Overview&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Funded by the National Science Foundation of China, this project aims to develop intelligent AR learning environments that utilize multi-channel information fusion to enhance student engagement and learning outcomes, for example, designing AR applications than embeded visual, auditory elements to enhance students&amp;rsquo; learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🛠️ Key Responsibilities
•	Designed and developed AR applications to investigate their effects on learning outcomes.
•	Designed an AR-data system to track student behaviors.
•	Explored AI integration in AR systems to deliver automatic, context-aware feedback to learners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🚀 Research Impact&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project contributes to the development of intelligent educational environments, enabling adaptive learning experiences and real-time feedback that support student-centered instruction.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AR to Enhance Students’ Representational Fluency</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/ar-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/ar-math/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Jul. 2018 - Mar. 2019 (Principal Investigator: Dr. Xiao Hu)
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
 --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🌟 Project Overview&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This joint research project, conducted in collaboration with Columbia University, Beijing Normal University, and East China Normal University, investigates how augmented reality (AR) can enhance students’ representational fluency and self-efficacy in understanding linear functions. The project focuses on designing and evaluating AR applications to support mathematical concept formation and problem-solving skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🛠️ Key Responsibilities
•	Developed 5 AR apps with varied design features to promote students’ understanding of linear functions.
•	Conducted Design-Based Research (DBR) to iteratively refine the apps and assess their impact on student learning.
•	Collected and analyzed data, including:
•	Quantitative Analysis: Conducted ANOVA to examine differences in learning outcomes.
•	Qualitative Analysis: Coded interviews and reflective journals to uncover patterns in students’ experiences.
•	Co-authored papers to disseminate findings and insights from the study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💡 Research Impact&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project demonstrates how leveraging AR can foster representational fluency and build students’ confidence in mathematical problem-solving. By combining innovative technology with evidence-based research, it contributes to the development of cutting-edge educational tools and pedagogical strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
